Chaithra KAKUNJE

Web Developer

124B rue du Kiem, Strassen Luxembourg – 8030 *⊅* +352 661376051

 □ chaithra.kashyap01@gmail.com



CAREER OBJECTIVE

Quality oriented web developer with 2+ years of experience with a proven knowledge of web platform development, web page content management, and website architecture. Aiming to leverage my skills to successfully fill the Web Developer role at your company.

SKILLS

HTML/CSS

JavaScript
jQuery

React
PHP

WordPress
Drupal
MySQL
GitHub

Apache Tomcat
Linux OS

EDUCATION

Master Of Computer Application

Visvesvaraya Technological University, India October 2012 – November 2015

Bachelor Of Computer Application

Alva's College, Moodbidri, India August 2008 – July 2011

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH HINDI

OTHER SKILLS

Search Engine Optimization
Logo Designing
Social media advertisement page design

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front End Web Developer at Animaker India Pvt Ltd, Bengaluru, India

July 2018 - April 2019

- O JavaScript based chrome extension development for screen recording
- Development and amendment of JavaScript and JSON files
- \circ $\:$ Web page design to start , pause and close the screen recording using Google API
- Web page with customized text editor design using React JavaScript for text to audio conversion application
- Front end development for text to Video conversion application using React JavaScript

Web Developer at G7CR Technologies India Pvt. Ltd, Bengaluru, India

June 2017 - June 2018

- Productive and positive team member involved in design, code, test, report and debug operations of Website development
 - O Web application security revamp and minimizing hacker attacks
 - O Post development cycle, website reverse walk through , identification & defects fixing
 - O Plugins and Theme management across multiple sites
 - O Network traffic and cross browser responsiveness tests
 - Microsoft Azure portal management, hosting, SSL integration

Junior Web Developer at SmartIdeas Inc, Bengaluru, India

January 2016 - May 2017

- O Requirement Analysis and website architecture design documentation
- Extensively worked on WordPress website design and development & hosting
- Worked on Database & Site performance optimization
- Implementation of SEO and site indexing to the first page of Google search result
- Site hosting with Digital Ocean and mapping it to custom domain with SSL integration